(this.webpackJsonptrivia_game=this.webpackJsonptrivia_game||[]).push([[0],{10:function(t,e,c){},12:function(t,e,c){"use strict";c.r(e);var r=c(1),n=c(5),s=c.n(n),o=c(2),i=(c(10),c(3)),a=c.p+"static/media/play.02df4387.mp3",u=c.p+"static/media/wrong.e9468218.mp3",x=c.p+"static/media/correct.160572d7.mp3",d=[{id:15,question:"?\u05d1\u05db\u05de\u05d4 \u05de\u05dc\u05d7\u05de\u05d5\u05ea \u05d5\u05de\u05d1\u05e6\u05e2\u05d9\u05dd \u05d4\u05e9\u05ea\u05ea\u05e4\u05d4 \u05d9\u05e9\u05e8\u05d0\u05dc \u05de\u05d0\u05d6 \u05e9\u05d4\u05d5\u05e7\u05de\u05d4",answers:[{text:"8",correct:!1},{text:"10",correct:!1},{text:"14",correct:!0},{text:"16",correct:!1}]},{id:1,question:"?\u05de\u05d4 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0 \u05e2\u05d9\u05e8 \u05d4\u05d1\u05d9\u05e8\u05d4 \u05e9\u05dc \u05d1\u05dc\u05d0\u05e8\u05d5\u05e1",answers:[{text:"\u05de\u05d9\u05e0\u05e1\u05e7",correct:!0},{text:"\u05d5\u05d9\u05dc\u05e0\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05e8\u05d9\u05d2\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d4\u05dc\u05e1\u05d9\u05e0\u05e7\u05d9",correct:!1}]},{id:2,question:"?\u05d0\u05d9\u05d6\u05d5 \u05de\u05d3\u05d9\u05e0\u05d4 \u05de\u05d1\u05d9\u05df \u05d4\u05d1\u05d0\u05d5\u05ea \u05d2\u05d3\u05d5\u05dc\u05d4 \u05d9\u05d5\u05ea\u05e8 \u05d1\u05e9\u05d8\u05d7 \u05e9\u05dc\u05d4",answers:[{text:"\u05d9\u05e8\u05d3\u05df",correct:!1},{text:"\u05de\u05e1\u05d5\u05e8\u05d9\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05e2\u05d9\u05e8\u05d0\u05e7",correct:!1},{text:"\u05de\u05e6\u05e8\u05d9\u05dd",correct:!0}]},{id:3,question:"?\u05d4\u05d9\u05db\u05df \u05d4\u05d5\u05de\u05e6\u05d0 \u05de\u05e9\u05d7\u05e7 \u05d4\u05dc\u05d2\u05d5",answers:[{text:"\u05e9\u05d5\u05d5\u05d3\u05d9\u05d4 ",correct:!1},{text:"\u05e4\u05d9\u05e0\u05dc\u05e0\u05d3",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d1\u05dc\u05d2\u05d9\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d3\u05e0\u05de\u05e8\u05e7 ",correct:!0}]},{id:4,question:"?\u05de\u05d4 \u05d4\u05d5\u05d0 \u05e9\u05d9\u05d0 \u05d4\u05e2\u05d5\u05dc\u05dd \u05d1\u05e8\u05d9\u05e6\u05ea 100 \u05de\u05d8\u05e8",answers:[{text:"9.54",correct:!1},{text:"9.58",correct:!0},{text:"9.61",correct:!1},{text:"9.67",correct:!1}]},{id:5,question:"?\u05db\u05d9\u05e6\u05d3 \u05de\u05db\u05d5\u05e0\u05d4 \u05de\u05e6\u05d1 \u05e9\u05dc \u05ea\u05d9\u05e7\u05d5 \u05d1\u05e9\u05d7\u05de\u05d8",answers:[{text:"\u05e4\u05dc",correct:!1},{text:"\u05e4\u05d8",correct:!0},{text:"\u05e9\u05d7",correct:!1},{text:"\u05e9\u05d7\u05e4\u05d8",correct:!1}]},{id:6,question:"?\u05e2\u05dc \u05e4\u05d9 \u05d4\u05de\u05e7\u05e8\u05d0 \u05de\u05d9 \u05de\u05e6\u05d0 \u05d0\u05ea \u05d4\u05de\u05dc\u05d5\u05db\u05d4 \u05db\u05e9\u05d4\u05dc\u05da \u05dc\u05d7\u05e4\u05e9 \u05d0\u05ea\u05d5\u05e0\u05d5\u05ea",answers:[{text:"\u05e9\u05d0\u05d5\u05dc",correct:!0},{text:"\u05d3\u05d5\u05d9\u05d3",correct:!1},{text:"\u05e9\u05dc\u05de\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05de\u05e9\u05d4",correct:!1}]},{id:7,question:"?\u05d1\u05d0\u05d9\u05d6\u05d5 \u05de\u05d3\u05d9\u05e0\u05d4 \u05e0\u05de\u05e6\u05d0\u05ea \u05d4\u05e2\u05d9\u05e8 \u05d0\u05d5\u05e1\u05dc\u05d5",answers:[{text:"\u05e9\u05d5\u05d5\u05d3\u05d9\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d3\u05e0\u05de\u05e8\u05e7",correct:!1},{text:"\u05e0\u05d5\u05e8\u05d5\u05d5\u05d2\u05d9\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d4\u05d5\u05e0\u05d2\u05e8\u05d9\u05d4",correct:!0}]},{id:8,question:"?\u05d4\u05d9\u05db\u05df \u05e0\u05de\u05e6\u05d0 \u05e2\u05de\u05e7 \u05d4\u05e1\u05d9\u05dc\u05d9\u05e7\u05d5\u05df \u05d1\u05d0\u05e8\u05d4\u05d1",answers:[{text:"\u05d0\u05d5\u05e8\u05dc\u05e0\u05d3\u05d5",correct:!1},{text:"\u05e0\u05d9\u05d5 \u05d9\u05d5\u05e8\u05e7",correct:!1},{text:"\u05e1\u05df \u05e4\u05e8\u05e0\u05e1\u05d9\u05e1\u05e7\u05d5",correct:!0},{text:"\u05de\u05d9\u05e0\u05d9\u05d0\u05e4\u05d5\u05dc\u05d9\u05e1",correct:!1}]},{id:9,question:"? \u05d1\u05e1\u05d9\u05e4\u05d5\u05e8 \u05d3\u05d9\u05e8\u05d4 \u05dc\u05d4\u05e9\u05db\u05d9\u05e8, \u05d0\u05d9\u05d6\u05d5 \u05d7\u05d9\u05d4 \u05e9\u05d5\u05db\u05e8\u05ea \u05dc\u05d1\u05e1\u05d5\u05e3 \u05d0\u05ea \u05d4\u05d3\u05d9\u05e8\u05d4",answers:[{text:"\u05e0\u05de\u05dc\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d9\u05d5\u05e0\u05d4",correct:!0},{text:"\u05d7\u05e4\u05e8\u05e4\u05e8\u05ea",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d0\u05e8\u05e0\u05d1\u05ea",correct:!1}]},{id:9,question:"?\u05d0\u05d9\u05d6\u05d4 \u05d0\u05d2\u05d5\u05d6\u05d9\u05dd \u05d4\u05dd \u05d4\u05de\u05e8\u05db\u05d9\u05d1 \u05d4\u05e2\u05d9\u05e7\u05e8\u05d9 \u05d1\u05de\u05de\u05e8\u05d7 \u05e0\u05d5\u05d8\u05dc\u05d4",answers:[{text:"\u05d0\u05d2\u05d5\u05d6\u05d9 \u05dc\u05d5\u05d6",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d0\u05d2\u05d5\u05d6\u05d9 \u05de\u05dc\u05da",correct:!0},{text:"\u05d0\u05d2\u05d5\u05d6\u05d9 \u05de\u05e7\u05d3\u05de\u05d9\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d0\u05d2\u05d5\u05d6\u05d9 \u05e4\u05e7\u05d0\u05df",correct:!1}]},{id:10,question:"?\u05d0\u05d9\u05d6\u05d4 \u05d0\u05d2\u05d5\u05d6\u05d9\u05dd \u05d4\u05dd \u05d4\u05de\u05e8\u05db\u05d9\u05d1 \u05d4\u05e2\u05d9\u05e7\u05e8\u05d9 \u05d1\u05de\u05de\u05e8\u05d7 \u05e0\u05d5\u05d8\u05dc\u05d4",answers:[{text:"\u05d0\u05d2\u05d5\u05d6\u05d9 \u05dc\u05d5\u05d6",correct:!0},{text:"\u05d0\u05d2\u05d5\u05d6\u05d9 \u05de\u05dc\u05da",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d0\u05d2\u05d5\u05d6\u05d9 \u05de\u05e7\u05d3\u05de\u05d9\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d0\u05d2\u05d5\u05d6\u05d9 \u05e4\u05e7\u05d0\u05df",correct:!1}]},{id:11,question:"?\u05d0\u05d9\u05d6\u05d4 \u05d0\u05d5\u05e7\u05d9\u05d9\u05e0\u05d5\u05e1 \u05d4\u05db\u05d9 \u05d2\u05d3\u05d5\u05dc",answers:[{text:"\u05d4\u05d0\u05d8\u05dc\u05e0\u05d8\u05d9",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d4\u05d4\u05d5\u05d3\u05d9",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d4\u05e9\u05e7\u05d8",correct:!0},{text:"\u05d4\u05d3\u05e8\u05d5\u05de\u05d9",correct:!1}]},{id:12,question:"?\u05d1\u05d0\u05d9\u05d6\u05d5 \u05e7\u05d1\u05d5\u05e6\u05d4 \u05e9\u05d9\u05d7\u05e7 \u05d4\u05db\u05d3\u05d5\u05e8\u05e1\u05dc\u05df \u05dc\u05d0\u05e8\u05d9 \u05d1\u05d9\u05e8\u05d3",answers:[{text:"\u05d0\u05d9\u05e0\u05d3\u05d9\u05d0\u05e0\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05e0\u05d9\u05e7\u05e1",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d1\u05d5\u05e1\u05d8\u05d5\u05df",correct:!0},{text:"\u05e9\u05d9\u05e7\u05d0\u05d2\u05d5",correct:!1}]},{id:13,question:"?\u05de\u05d4 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d1\u05e9\u05ea \u05d4\u05d2\u05d3\u05d5\u05dc\u05d4 \u05d1\u05e2\u05d5\u05dc\u05dd",answers:[{text:"\u05d0\u05e1\u05d9\u05d4",correct:!0},{text:"\u05d0\u05d9\u05e8\u05d5\u05e4\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d0\u05e4\u05e8\u05d9\u05e7\u05d4",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d0\u05de\u05e8\u05d9\u05e7\u05d4 \u05d4\u05e6\u05e4\u05d5\u05e0\u05d9\u05ea",correct:!1}]},{id:14,question:"?\u05de\u05d4 \u05d4\u05d9\u05d0 \u05d4\u05e2\u05d9\u05e8 \u05e2\u05dd \u05d4\u05d0\u05d5\u05db\u05dc\u05d5\u05e1\u05d9\u05d4 \u05d4\u05db\u05d9 \u05d2\u05d3\u05d5\u05dc\u05d4 \u05d1\u05e2\u05d5\u05dc\u05dd",answers:[{text:"\u05e9\u05d0\u05e0\u05d2\u05d7\u05d0\u05d9",correct:!0},{text:"\u05de\u05d5\u05de\u05d1\u05d0\u05d9",correct:!1},{text:"\u05d1\u05d5\u05d0\u05e0\u05d5\u05e1 \u05d0\u05d9\u05d9\u05e8\u05e1",correct:!1},{text:"\t\u05d0\u05d9\u05e1\u05d8\u05e0\u05d1\u05d5\u05dc",correct:!1}]}],m=c(0);var j=function(t){var e=t.setTimer,c=t.questionNumber,n=t.setQuestionNumber,s=Object(r.useState)(null),j=Object(o.a)(s,2),l=j[0],b=j[1],O=Object(r.useState)(null),f=Object(o.a)(O,2),v=f[0],w=f[1],N=Object(r.useState)("answer"),h=Object(o.a)(N,2),p=h[0],q=h[1],$=Object(i.a)(a),y=Object(o.a)($,1)[0],I=Object(i.a)(x),S=Object(o.a)(I,1)[0],g=Object(i.a)(u),T=Object(o.a)(g,1)[0];Object(r.useEffect)((function(){y()}),[]);var E=function(t,e){setTimeout((function(){e()}),t)};return Object(r.useEffect)((function(){b(d[c-1])}),[d,c]),Object(m.jsxs)("div",{className:"trivia",children:[Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"question",children:null===l||void 0===l?void 0:l.question}),Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"answers",children:null===l||void 0===l?void 0:l.answers.map((function(t){return Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:v===t?p:"answer",onClick:function(){return function(t){w(t),q("answer active"),E(3e3,(function(){q(t.correct?"answer correct":"answer wrong")})),E(5e3,(function(){t.correct?(S(),E(1e3,(function(){n((function(t){return t+1})),w(null)}))):(T(),E(1e3,(function(){e(!0)})))}))}(t)},children:t.text},t.id)}))})]})};function l(t){var e=t.setTimer,c=t.questionNumber,n=Object(r.useState)(30),s=Object(o.a)(n,2),i=s[0],a=s[1];return Object(r.useEffect)((function(){if(0===i)return e(!0);var t=setInterval((function(){a((function(t){return t-1}))}),1e3);return function(){return clearInterval(t)}}),[i,e]),Object(r.useEffect)((function(){a(30)}),[c]),i}var b=function(t){var e=t.setUserName,c=Object(r.useRef)();return Object(m.jsxs)("div",{className:"start",children:[Object(m.jsx)("input",{className:"startInput",placeholder:"enter your name",ref:c}),Object(m.jsx)("button",{className:"startButton",onClick:function(){c.current.value&&e(c.current.value)},children:"Start"})]})},O=[{id:1,amount:"$100"},{id:2,amount:"$200"},{id:3,amount:"$300"},{id:4,amount:"$500"},{id:5,amount:"$700"},{id:6,amount:"$900"},{id:7,amount:"$1500"},{id:8,amount:"$2000"},{id:9,amount:"$2500"},{id:10,amount:"$3000"},{id:11,amount:"$4000"},{id:12,amount:"$5000"},{id:13,amount:"$6000"},{id:14,amount:"$8000"},{id:15,amount:"$10,000"}].reverse();var f=function(){var t=Object(r.useState)(1),e=Object(o.a)(t,2),c=e[0],n=e[1],s=Object(r.useState)(null),i=Object(o.a)(s,2),a=i[0],u=i[1],x=Object(r.useState)(!1),d=Object(o.a)(x,2),f=d[0],v=d[1],w=Object(r.useState)(0),N=Object(o.a)(w,2),h=N[0],p=N[1];return Object(r.useEffect)((function(){c>1&&p(O.find((function(t){return t.id===c-1})).amount)}),[O,c]),Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:a?Object(m.jsxs)(m.Fragment,{children:[Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"main",children:f?Object(m.jsxs)("h1",{className:"endText",children:[a," You earned:",h,Object(m.jsx)("button",{className:"reload",onClick:function(){window.location.reload()},children:"Try agian"})]}):Object(m.jsxs)(m.Fragment,{children:[Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"top",children:Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"timer",children:Object(m.jsx)(l,{setTimer:v,questionNumber:c})})}),Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"bottom",children:Object(m.jsx)(j,{setQuestionNumber:n,questionNumber:c,setTimer:v})})]})}),Object(m.jsx)("div",{className:"money",children:Object(m.jsx)("ul",{className:"moneyList",children:O.map((function(t){return Object(m.jsxs)("li",{className:c===t.id?"moneyListItem active":"moneyListItem",children:[Object(m.jsx)("span",{className:"moneyLIstItemNumber",children:t.id}),Object(m.jsx)("span",{className:"moneyLIstItemNumberAmount",children:t.amount}),f]},t.id)}))})})]}):Object(m.jsx)(b,{setUserName:u})})};s.a.render(Object(m.jsx)(f,{}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[12,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.e2344320.chunk.js.map